[
    {
      "num": "1",
      "question": "각주",
      "answer": "구검",
      "options": ["부심", "구검", "지계", "난제"]
    },
    {
      "num": "2",
      "question": "견물",
      "answer": "생심",
      "options": ["이락", "지족", "양난", "생심"]
    },
    {
      "num": "3",
      "question": "국리",
      "answer": "민복",
      "options": ["양난", "인수", "생심", "민복"]
    },
    {
      "num": "4",
      "question": "난형",
      "answer": "난제",
      "options": ["구검", "호제", "재천", "난제"]
    },
    {
      "num": "5",
      "question": "능대",
      "answer": "능소",
      "options": ["난망", "구검", "능소", "지물"]
    },
    {
      "num": "6",
      "question": "마이",
      "answer": "동풍",
      "options": ["지리", "지계", "동풍", "살우"]
    },
    {
      "num": "7",
      "question": "무용",
      "answer": "지물",
      "options": ["지물", "해지", "동풍", "생심"]
    },
    {
      "num": "8",
      "question": "문일",
      "answer": "지십",
      "options": ["부심", "봉대", "무환", "지십"]
    },
    {
      "num": "9",
      "question": "명경",
      "answer": "지수",
      "options": ["인수", "지수", "동풍", "난망"]
    },
    {
      "num": "10",
      "question": "백골",
      "answer": "난망",
      "options": ["명월", "부심", "지족", "난망"]
    },
    {
      "num": "11",
      "question": "사면",
      "answer": "초가",
      "options": ["초가", "지수", "오면", "양난"]
    },
    {
      "num": "12",
      "question": "삼한",
      "answer": "사온",
      "options": ["사온", "살우", "사한", "난망"]
    },
    {
      "num": "13",
      "question": "신토",
      "answer": "불이",
      "options": ["지족", "해지", "불이", "봉대"]
    },
    {
      "num": "14",
      "question": "아전",
      "answer": "인수",
      "options": ["인수", "해지", "양난", "불이"]
    },
    {
      "num": "15",
      "question": "오비",
      "answer": "이락",
      "options": ["이락", "초가", "재천", "당착"]
    },
    {
      "num": "16",
      "question": "유비",
      "answer": "무환",
      "options": ["무완", "무한", "무환", "무안"]
    },
    {
      "num": "17",
      "question": "인명",
      "answer": "재천",
      "options": ["재천", "명월", "지세", "동풍"]
    },
    {
      "num": "18",
      "question": "안분",
      "answer": "지족",
      "options": ["구검", "부심", "이락", "지족"]
    },
    {
      "num": "19",
      "question": "자가",
      "answer": "당착",
      "options": ["구검", "당착", "복검", "양난"]
    },
    {
      "num": "20",
      "question": "절치",
      "answer": "부심",
      "options": ["유심", "지계", "부심", "봉대"]
    },
    {
      "num": "21",
      "question": "진퇴",
      "answer": "양난",
      "options": ["양난", "지세", "앙난", "불이"]
    },
    {
      "num": "22",
      "question": "침소",
      "answer": "봉대",
      "options": ["붕대", "민복", "지계", "봉대"]
    },
    {
      "num": "23",
      "question": "청풍",
      "answer": "명월",
      "options": ["불이", "난망", "명월", "구검"]
    },
    {
      "num": "24",
      "question": "타산",
      "answer": "지석",
      "options": ["지석", "민복", "지수", "부심"]
    },
    {
      "num": "25",
      "question": "파죽",
      "answer": "지세",
      "options": ["지세", "복검", "불이", "살우"]
    },
    {
      "num": "26",
      "question": "관포",
      "answer": "지교",
      "options": ["지고", "지교", "명월", "생심"]
    },
    {
      "num": "27",
      "question": "결자",
      "answer": "해지",
      "options": ["해지", "혜지", "훼지", "회지"]
    },
    {
      "num": "28",
      "question": "교각",
      "answer": "살우",
      "options": ["생심", "살우", "지석", "지십"]
    },
    {
      "num": "29",
      "question": "구밀",
      "answer": "복검",
      "options": ["하석", "봉대", "복검", "구검"]
    },
    {
      "num": "30",
      "question": "금란",
      "answer": "지계",
      "options": ["지계", "명월", "무환", "지물"]
    }
  ]
  